homescan.com 2004-06-03

# ACNielsen: Privacy Policy

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how ACNielsen collects, uses and safeguards personal information provided to us on our website.

#### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

We are committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this site. Accordingly, at this site, we do not collect personally identifying information from users unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly.

When you visit our site, your browser automatically sends us an IP (Internet Protocol) address and certain other information, including the type of browser you use. We may use this IP address and other information to give you access to the site and otherwise administer the site. In certain parts of the site, we may ask you to provide us with your name, title, street address, company, telephone and fax numbers and certain other personal information so that we can provide you with information you request. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information but, without it, we cannot provide you the information you request.

The site also may include certain features that allow you to communicate with us by electronic mail or otherwise. If an electronic mail feature is provided and you choose to use it, you will provide us with your e-mail address and some or all of the information described above. We do not solicit any other personally identifying information, so you are responsible if you choose to use these communication features to provide additional personally identifying information to us. When you provide any personally identifying information to us, you communicate that you are knowingly and voluntarily providing us the information.

We try to make sure that the personally identifying information you provide us remains private. We will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose the personally identifying information you provide to anyone outside of ACNielsen Corporation, its parent, subsidiaries and affiliated companies, and our respective contractors providing services to us (but in that case, information is disclosed only for purposes of providing those services) unless we are required by law or have a good faith basis that you are in violation of the terms of service of our site or federal, state or local laws. We will use the personally identifying information to respond to your requests.

When you use the site, you consent to the transmission of your personally identifying information to us and to its use as described herein. We will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us via this site in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

We may release information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law or to protect our rights.

In the event that ACNielsen Corporation or substantially all of its assets were sold or otherwise transferred or acquired, various forms of information may be included among the transferred assets.

#### Cookies and Usage Information

Like many companies, we use "cookie" technology on our site. These cookies may tell us whether you have visited our site before or are a new visitor and what material on our site you have viewed. The cookies we use do not collect any personally identifying information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookies do not extract any information from your computer. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, [Site Seeing on the Internet](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html).

You should also be aware that we collect certain usage information about our site, such as the number and frequency of visitors to certain parts of the site. We may use this information for research or to improve our site. This data is used only in the aggregate and does not include any personally identifying information.

#### Children's Privacy

We do not intentionally collect information at our website from those we actually know to be under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### How to Request Access to or Correction of Information We Collect from You

You can access the personally identifiable information that we collect from you online and maintain by contacting **[Myung Yim](mailto:Myung.Yim@acnielsen.com), Content Operations Manager, ACNielsen, 770 Broadway, New York, NY 10003-9596, USA, +1 646 654 8194**. You can request that we correct factual errors in personally identifiable information about you by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### Conditions of Use and Changes to This Policy

If you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including limitations on damages and application of the laws of the state of Delaware. If you have any concern about privacy at ACNielsen, please send a thorough description to Senior Vice President, Global Communications, ACNielsen Corporation, 770 Broadway, New York, NY 10003-9596, USA, and we will try to resolve it.

We reserve the right to update and make changes to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service and to materially change our practices in handling information, including personally identifiable information. If we do make such changes, we will post notice of those changes either at this location on our website or elsewhere on the website in a prominent location. Our use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

You may request a copy of the Privacy Policy we posted prior to the web updates made to this document.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to this site only, and not to other sites, including the separate sites of ACNielsen Answers, ACNielsen BASES, ACNielsen.Online, ACNielsen eRatings.com, ReelResearch, NetDispatch and Strategic Planner.

#### Any questions?

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please call ACNielsen Global Communications at +1 203 961 3324 or email us at [webmaster@acnielsen.com](mailto:webmaster@acnielsen.com).
